Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Goku and Freeza alone remain on Planet Namek,
which is mere moments from annihilation.
I've been waiting for this moment.
The moment when just the two of us
can fight to our hearts' content.
Hmph, it sounds like you want to
settle the score with me, Freeza,
no matter what.
Dokkan Dokkan tsuite'ru
Dokkan Dokkan paradise
Genki dama ga hajiketobu ze
Go Go Let's do it
Ugomeku ayashii enajii
yousha wa shinai ze mite'ro yo
Inochi ni kaete mo mamoru yo
Ai suru yuuki wo tsuyosa ni kaero
Yarinuku kiai de pinchi wo koete'ku
Tegowai yatsu hodo wakuwaku mo dekkai ze
Dokkan Dokkan tsuite'ru
Dokkan Dokkan Chansu sa
Rakkii no kaze ni byunbyun notte
Dokkan Dokkan tsuite'ru
Dokkan Dokkan ashita mo
kotae wo mou tamashii wa shitte'ru no sa
Dragon Soul!
"The Two Who Remain On a Vanishing Planet!
This is the Final Showdown. "
Bulma-san!
G-Gohan-kun...
Gohan-kun, what was the big idea,
making me wait all that time alone?
I'm sorry.
Where exactly are we?
It doesn't appear to be Planet Namek.
l was aboard the spaceship.
I don't see the spaceship around here.
l-lt's you...
Where are we?
Son!
Piccolo-san!
--Gohan...
--Piccolo-san! Ah, Dende!
Am I dreaming?
Ow! This isn't a dream!
It looks like I've come back to life.
Then, has Kuririn-san, too?
I don't know.
Yeah, I guess not.
G-Grand Elder!
Grand Elder?
One way or another, you're going
to be dead in a few minutes.
You poor, pathetic creature.
You're the pathetic one.
After all, you're the one
who's about to be beaten by a
detestable, simian Saiyan bastard.
Hmph, it doesn't matter how
much bravado you put forth.
I'm the one who will be
watching this planet explode!
Everyone, this is the planet Earth.
--Earth?!
--|-|t can't be! How?
What has happened here?
My time is short, and I will
once again be called away.
But before I die,
I would like to relate to you
what has just happened to us.
Where have Kakarrot and
Freeza disappeared to?
Then, Father is still fighting
Freeza on Planet Namek?
Grand Elder, do you know what
has become of Planet Namek?
Unfortunately, I am no longer
aware of the happenings on Namek.
O-Oh, no...
Son will be fine.
Piccolo-san...
Of course he'll be fine.
P-Piccolo-san...
Father...
Son-kun, don't you die.
Son...
Father”
Hmph! There's no way I
can lose to some monkey!
Not to a mere Saiyan monkey!
Goku! Goku!
Kaio-sama, what is happening?
Th-They're evenly-matched. Goku is
fighting toe-to-toe against Freeza.
But there's no time left
before Planet Namek explodes.
If their fight keeps going like this,
it will play right into Freeza's hands.
How exactly do you mean?
When Planet Namek is destroyed, Goku will die.
However, Freeza will survive.
He is able to live in any environment.
Kaio-sama, isn't there any way to save Goku?
This is the path that Goku chose for himself.
O-Oh, no...
--Yamucha!
--Goku!
S-Son...
How do you like this?! I will not
be beaten by an inferior Saiyan!
Not by a lowly Saiyan!
You monkey!!
What are you doing, Bulma-san?
A little botanomancy. I learned
how to do this when I was a child.
To pray for the safe return of a traveler,
you put three leaves inside
a circle and burn them.
They say that if the leaves all burn up,
the traveler will come home safely.
Oh, and you're divining Goku's fate, right?
Look, they're burning!
I'm sure they'll all burn up.
Goku-san will be coming home, right?
Yeah! This kind of
fortune-telling is always right!
Fortune-telling is a bunch of baloney!
Father is definitely coming home!
Yeah, you're right!
Father is going to beat Freeza
and come home for sure!
How about that, you simian bastard?
Is that all you've got?
What?
| asked you if that was all you've got.
H-How insolent!
You simian bastard!
You're just a lowly Saiyan!
D-Damn it...
I'll pay you back for this tenfold--
no, a hundredfold!
--|'m calling it.
--W-What?
W-What do you mean, you're calling it?
The backlash from you using
your 100-percent power
has you past your peak,
and your Ki is dropping in a hurry.
I'm beginning to think there ain't
no reason to fight you no further.
I'm satisfied. Your pride is already in tatters.
After all, someone showed
up who surpassed you--
something you thought no one
in the world could ever do.
What's more, he turned out to be...
...a "lowly Saiyan."
Now that you're this spooked,
there ain't no point in defeating you.
You should go on living with
that shock, quietly, in obscurity.
I'm going home to Earth.
If I leave now, I should
still barely make it in time.
Freeza, don't you ever cause any trouble again.
I don't ever wanna see your face again.
Don't you screw around...
Don't you screw around with me!
l-l'm not...
I'm not...
...beaten!!
You're a complete and utter fool!
I gave you one last chance!
Freeza!!
That will follow you anywhere you go!
And it will also slice through anything!
Hmph! | see through your strategy!
You're going to come toward me,
turning away at the last second,
to try to get it to hit me, right?!
Do you think I'm going to fall
for a two-bit tactic like that?!
Come on!
Gotcha!
Over here, Freeza!
Hmph, an afterimage, huh?
Not too shabby, monkey.
Sure enough, I have absolutely
no desire to fight you now.
Not if you're pinning your hopes
on a bush-league move like that.
If you really want to settle this,
build up your strength again,
and hone your skills some more.
A bush-league move, is it?
Goku! There's no time!
Planet Namek is going to explode!
Father!!
M-My technique is a bush-league move, is it?
Then how about two of them?!
You just don't get it.
Monkey, those will follow you
no matter where you go!
You think you can get away
from them? You'll be cut to pieces!
Freeza, you never learn!
Hmph! The same pattern, huh?
You've got no style!
Damn it! lam not falling for that childish trick!
Where are you, you simian bastard?!
You're no match for me!
I will not be shown up by any simian bastard!
Don't get up! Stay down!
l-lt can't be...!
K-Kaio-sama, what is the matter?
D-Don't tell us Goku has lost!
F-Freeza has been...
...cut in half...
The endgame is at hand.
Yaburekabure omoikiri
Tobu n da mugen no sora e
Jetto kiryuu ni nokkari
doko demo iku yo sokkou
Mukoumizu tte saikou
Let's go tip-top! All right?
Me mo sameru you na aoi chikyuu
kakegaenai kono hoshi yuzurenai kara
Hajiketobase kamehameha
Yabame no kono jidai
sekai wo mamoru tame umareta kara
Yaburekabure omoikiri
Yaru n da furupawaa
Kibou ga ore no buki dakara
mirai shinjite
You may have brought that upon
yourself, but what a miserable end.
Damn it! Damn it!
You'll share the same fate as the
planet you've destroyed, Freeza!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z Kai,
"Son Goku's Final Attack...
Planet Namek Passes On into Space. "
Please... help me...