Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Goku had finally achieved victory. However...
Damn it all!!
Is Son Goku dead?
Dokkan Dokkan tsuite'ru
Dokkan Dokkan paradise
Genki dama ga hajiketobu ze
Go Go Let's do it
Ugomeku ayashii enajii
yousha wa shinai ze mite'ro yo
Inochi ni kaete mo mamoru yo
Ai suru yuuki wo tsuyosa ni kaero
Yarinuku kiai de pinchi wo koete'ku
Tegowai yatsu hodo wakuwaku mo dekkai ze
Dokkan Dokkan tsuite'ru
Dokkan Dokkan Chansu sa
Rakkii no kaze ni byunbyun notte
Dokkan Dokkan tsuite'ru
Dokkan Dokkan ashita mo
kotae wo mou tamashii wa shitte'ru no sa
Dragon Soul!
"Goku Vanishes into Space...
Back to Life, Super Warriors!”
Kaio-sama...
Is Goku really...?
Sure enough, there's no hope.
Damn it! Goku!
He really is dead, then?
What a shame.
We'll have to inform Goku's son
on Earth of his father's death.
This will be hard on him.
What if we have Bulma-san tell him?
All right.
Please, let me be the one to tell her.
Okay then, Yamucha.
Well then, if you would...
Right.
Bulma... Bulma, can you hear me?
Bulma...
Can you hear me, Bulma?
It's me, Yamucha.
Huh? Yamucha?
That's right. It's Yamucha.
I'm speaking directly into
your mind through Kaio-sama.
Into my mind?
ReaHy?
What is it, Bulma-san?
By any chance, is that Kaio-sama?
That's what he said.
I'm impressed that you knew.
Yamucha is the one speaking right now.
So, are you doing well, Yamucha?
Mm-hmm. lam still dead,
but I'm doing fine, otherwise.
But never mind me, I want you
to keep calm and listen to me.
It's about Goku.
Goku defeated Freeza. B-But then...
Hey, everyone, listen up! He says
that Son-kun has taken down Freeza!
Really, Bulma-san? Hooray! Hooray!
Hooray! Hooray!
He has, huh? Son, you finally did it.
Father has won! He won!
Freeza, beaten by Kakarrot?
Be quiet and listen to me.
There's more than just that.
After he defeated Freeza, Goku...
...desperately tried to get away, but...
...he didn't make it before
Planet Namek exploded...
...and he died.
Hey, hold up, everyone.
He says that Son-kun died
when Planet Namek exploded.
That's a shocker, huh?
You dumbass! How can you put it like that?!
Think about Gohan, will you?!
Goku can never come back again!
You don't know what's what.
We have the Dragon Balls from Planet Namek.
The Dragon Balls came to Earth
together with the Namekians.
This will surprise you!
They say that the Namekian Dragon Balls
can bring people back
to life over and over again!
In other words, Son-kun,
Kuririn-kun, and Chaozu-kun
can all come back to life again.
l-ls that right?!
What is it, Yamucha?
We're all coming back to life!
Including you, Chaozu.
ReaHy?
It's the folks on Earth who
don't know what's what.
Sure, Chaozu can be brought back to life
with the Namekian Dragon Balls.
But as for Goku and Kuririn...
What about Goku and Kuririn, Kaio-sama?
The Dragon Balls bring the dead
back to life where they died.
Which means...?
Goku and Kuririn would come
back to life on Planet Namek.
However, Planet Namek is no longer there!
It's now just the vacuum of space.
Death would be waiting for them
the moment they returned to life.
Kaio-sama, with your power,
can't you... can't you do anything?
I can do nothing. That place
is not under myjurisdiction.
H-He says that Son-kun... can't come back.
O-Oh, no...!
W-Why is it that Father and
Kuririn-san can't come home alive?
It sounds like if Kami-sama
regenerated your body,
like in Chaozu-kun's case,
and you're there at
Kaio-sama's place, you'd be fine,
but otherwise, you come back
to life wherever you died.
But Son-kun and Kuririn-kun
died on Planet Namek, and...
Planet Namek isn't there anymore, right?
It's just the vacuum of space.
What's more, apparently,
Kaio-sama isn't in charge
of the area where Planet Namek is.
O-Oh, no...
Why don't you try using
your heads for a minute?
You can just relocate their souls,
or whatever they are, here to Earth,
and then revive them, right?
More than likely.
Yeah! He's right!
That's a pretty good idea you had, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
Don't get carried away.
Ijust want to see Kakarrot,
now that he's a Super Saiyan.
And then, someday, I'll beat him. I swear it!
E-Excuse me, my earthling friend...
Once the Dragon Balls of Namek are restored,
we plan to locate a suitable
world and relocate there.
Could you direct us to a place
where we can spend our time until then?
Well, okay.
In that case, you can stay at my home.
Are you sure about that?
It's a huge place, so no problem.
Besides, we'd like to make use of
your Dragon Balls a little bit more.
Do it! Right, Dende-kun?
Sure...
If this many of you are
spotted loitering around,
it will create a huge uproar.
That's true enough.
Okay, we'll take you up on it.
How about you coming, too?
After all, you've got no hotel money, right?
l'll feed you plenty.
I'll bet you're just like Son-kun,
and eat like crazy, right?
But no matter how attractive I
might be, no hanky panky, okay?
V-Vulgar woman! Keep your voice down.
Okay, everyone, sit tight for a minute.
I'll go hunt down a phone
somewhere and have my dad come.
U-Um, Bulma-san...
Could I maybe stay over at
your place, too, Bulma-san?
Gohan-kun, you have your
own house, don't you?
You should go home. Your mother
must be worried about you.
Yeah, well, you see...
| forgot to do my homework...
and Mother will be angry with me.
Faster! Faster! Doesn't this
thing have more speed?!
Aw, geez...
Ah, he's here! He's here, he's here!
Here we are! Here! Here! Here we are!
Gohan-chan!
Where is Gohan-chan?!
Mother, I'm home.
And so, the Namekians were
taken to the Capsule Corporation.
This is my home. What do you think?
Pretty cushy place, huh?
Is that...?
And so, the Namekians ended
up staying at Bulma's home
until the Dragon Balls became reactivated.
And then, in no time at all,
130 days had passed.
Wow. The Namekian Dragon Balls
reactivate after only 130 days, huh?
That's right. A Namekian
year is 130 days, after all.
That's about one-third of what
it is on Earth. Nice, isn't it?
Well, let's make our wishes to
Super Shen Long, right away.
J-Just a minute. Gohan isn't here yet.
Hey! Hold up a sec!
--Hey, Gohan!
Sorry, my cram school ran a little long.
You're going to cram school
again? What a little trooper.
I want to have my Gohan-chan study like crazy,
so he'll end up becomin' a great scholar.
Well, we were just about to get started.
Okay, Dende-kun, if you please.
Right.
Takkaraputo Poppolunga pupirito paro!
Whoo! Whoo!
So this is the original Shen Long...
Wow, this is incredible!
Oh, my!
Thou who hast gathered
the seven Dragon Balls,
I shall grant thee any three wishes.
My earthling friend, we can go next time.
Go ahead and have your wishes granted.
Thank you very much, Grand Elder.
All right then, we'll make our wishes.
First, summon the souls
of Son Goku and Kuririn,
who died on Planet Namek, to come here.
Napahito sonda bakuli Iepicatto sopaIetto!
Understood. I shall try.
l have called hither the soul
of the one called Kuririn.
However, I cannot call forth the
soul of the one called Son Goku.
Huh? O-Oh, no! Why not?
Because Son Goku is alive.
I cannot call forth only his soul.
H-H-He's alive?
W-What?
H-He couldn't be. How?
--Yay! Yay!
Hooray!
If he's alive, I wonder why he hasn't come home.
His spaceship is probably
damaged or something.
Oh, in that case, you can ask
Polunga to summon him here.
Yeah, right!
Yay!
Okay then, first, the second wish.
--Go on! Go on!
--Bring Kuririn back to life.
Papitto Iatonguge Kuririn barsatto!
H-Huh?
Kuririn-san!
O-Oh, right. I've come back to life.
--Hooray!
--Yay! Yay!
As a special deal,
I have restored his dismembered
body to its original form.
You may have a stern face,
but you do good work, don't you?
Now then, finally,
pick up Son-kun and deliver him here!
--Hooray!
--Yay! Yay!
Hirokelotto deliba milocasuta pippo!
Goku-sa...
I cannot.
I have been denied.
The man named Son says that he
will return on his own in due time.
D-Denied? But why?
I know why!
He's afraid of his wife!
The strongest one in the universe
is Super Saiyan Son Goku's wife!
J-Joking! I'm joking!
F-Father isn't coming back?
He said he would come back
on his own in due time.
He's definitely coming home.
Iget it. He's training on another planet,
with plans to power up even more.
I can't just stick around here,
spinning my wheels!
Oh, dear...
Pay him no mind.
Keep going. Instead of Son,
bring back to life someone at Kaio's place.
Yeah, right. I wonder who we should ask for.
They say they want to call one of you back.
What should we do?
I want to train here for a little while longer.
I-I'd like to stay with Ten-san.
Okay then, Yamucha, you're the one to go.
Me first, huh? Sorry, guys.
All right. Well then...
Bulma... Bulma...
Bulma, it's me. Do you know who I am?
Kaio-sama?
Tenshinhan and Chaozu will be
staying over here a little longer.
Bring Yamucha back to life.
Yamucha, huh? Okay.
All right, the third wish. Once more, please!
Bring Yamucha back to life!
Pipatto dominori keludemine coaIutto!
All right, understood.
I have brought the man
called Yamucha back to life.
--Where? Huh? W-Where is he?
--Where? Where?
I have now granted all of thy wishes. Farewell!
J-Just a minute!
Aw, he's gone. Where is Yamucha?
Over here!
Ribbit-ribbit!
Yamucha-sama!
--Ribbit... ribbit...
--Yamucha-sama! Yamucha-sama!
Pu-erh...
Yamucha...
As long as you were going to bring me back,
I wish you could have picked a better spot.
And so, another 130 days passed.
With the first wish, Chaozu...
--Yahoo!
--Welcome home!
...and with the second wish,
Tenshinhan came back to life.
Ten-san...
--Ten-san! Ten-san!
--Chaozu...
And then...
Okay, Dende, it's time for us to take our leave.
R-Right.
Thank you very much, everyone.
T-Take care, okay?
Gohan-san, goodbye.
I've really enjoyed myself.
Dende...?
Dende...
Picoleto camuleo zecanpile...
I shall grant that wish.
Goodbye.
Goodbye...
Goodbye!
G—G...
Goodbye...
With the third wish, the Namekians
moved to another world.
Let's see...
And so, for a short while,
the peace on Earth continued. However...
Yaburekabure omoikiri
Tobu n da mugen no sora e
Jetto kiryuu ni nokkari
doko demo iku yo sokkou
Mukoumizu tte saikou
Let's go tip-top! All right?
Me mo sameru you na aoi chikyuu
kakegaenai kono hoshi yuzurenai kara
Hajiketobase kamehameha
Yabame no kono jidai
sekai wo mamoru tame umareta kara
Yaburekabure omoikiri
Yaru n da furupawaa
Kibou ga ore no buki dakara
mirai shinjite
It's been a year now, but still,
Father has not returned home.
I wonder if he really is afraid of Mother.
Hey, Gohan, there's an evil Ki approaching!
This Ki couldn't belong to Freeza, could it?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z Kai,
"That There Is Earth, Papa...
Freeza and Father Strike Back. ”
Goku, I thought you finished him off!