Edited at https://subtitletools.com
An unexpected conclusion laid in store
for the final showdown on Planet Namek.
Don't get up!
|-|t can't be...!
Dokkan Dokkan We're in luck
Dokkan Dokkan Paradise
The Genki Dama bursts away
Go Go Let's do it
There's a wriggling, mysterious energy
I won't hold back, just you watch
l'll protect you with my life
Turn your courage to love into strength
We'll overcome crises with carry-through spirit
The tougher your opponent is,
the greater the excitement
Dokkan Dokkan We're in luck
Dokkan Dokkan Now's our chance
Whooshing along on the lucky wind
Dokkan Dokkan We're in luck
Dokkan Dokkan Tomorrow, as well
Your soul already knows the answer
Dragon Soul!
"Son Goku's Final Attack...
Planet Namek Passes On into Space. "
Sure, you may have brought that upon yourself,
but it ain't like you to meet
such a miserable end.
I'll get back to Earth somehow.
You'll share the same fate as the
planet that you yourself destroyed.
Help...
H-Help...
H-Help... m-me...
Goku, what are you waiting for?
Get out of there, now!
P-Please... h-h...
...help... me...!
Help...
Help... me...!
It's always about you!
How many... How many people have you killed
as they begged for their lives,
like you're doing?!
Please... help me...!
Please...!
Freeza...
I've shared a small amount of my Ki with you.
You should be able to get around
well enough, even in your shape.
You can manage the rest on your own!
This is unexpected.
Y-You, sharing your energy with me...
...you simian bastard...!
You can survive in the vacuum of space, right?
Then hurry up and get off of this planet.
Live on, and fully realize how precious life is!
P-Planet Namek here is just
moments from exploding.
Where do you think you're going?
No matter what you do, you can't
live in the vacuum of space.
Death is all that awaits you.
There's no more time before it explodes!
You don't have any time to
make it back to your spaceship!
And Vegeta has wrecked
the spaceship that I came in.
You Saiyans really are simian bastards!
You can't get off of this planet!
You're going to perish, right along with it!
How ironic. You, who won the fight, will die,
while I will be spared!
Th-That's what you get for being so insolent
as to share your energy with me, Freeza.
|'|| survive, just you watch.
I'm calling it.
W-What?
W-What do you mean, you're calling it?
I'm beginning to think there ain't
no reason to fight you no further.
You should go on living with
that shock, quietly, in obscurity.
S-Simian bastard...!
lam the greatest in the universe!
lam the cosmic emperor, Freeza!
Th-That's why you...
...you simian bastard...
...must die by my hand!
Y-You...
...deserve...
...to be killed by me!
You dumbass!!
Here...
Th-Thank you.
Wait up!
Up here!
It appears that my time is almost here.
G-Grand Elder!
G-Grand Elder...!
--Grand Elder!
Grand Elder!
G-Gather... Gather everyone here.
Right!
--Grand Elder!
It would seem that the time has
come for me to take my leave.
|-| am glad that l was able to live a full life.
Muri-sama!
Yes, what did you find?
Sure enough, we cannot locate
anyone from Elder Tsuno's village.
What could have become of them?
Those are probably the guys
from the village that l wiped out.
The wish to the Dragon Balls
was to bring back to life
everyone that was killed by
Freeza and his men, right?
Hmph, I am not one of Freeza's men.
Botched that one up, huh?
Oh, the Dragon Balls appear...
to have followed us here.
G-Grand Elder...!
A-As I said earlier, my time is now all but up.
M-Muri...
Y-Yes?
Hold... Hold out your hand.
Right.
F-From here on, you will be the Grand Elder.
l-ln time, the Dragon Balls will
once again regain their brilliance.
Use the Dragon Balls well.
Y-Yes, as you wish.
|-| leave you to it.
Grand Elder!
P-Peace on Namek, forever...
Grand Elder...
G-Grand Elder...
G... Grand Elder...
Grand Elder, may you rest in peace.
|-| now understand clearly, Piccolo-san.
You merged with Nail-san, didn't you?
G-Guys!
The Grand Elder is now gone.
Let those of us who are left behind
join together to usher in an everlasting peace!
--Right!
--|ndeed!
The Grand Elder has passed away,
and Kuririn-kun won't be
coming back, either, huh?
No. Someone who has been
returned to life with the Dragon Balls
cannot be brought back a second time.
Eh? It's all right!
Namek's Dragon Balls can
restore life again and again!
As long as it wasn't a natural death,
there's probably no limit.
So then... then...
Dende, when the day comes that
we can have our wishes granted
by your Dragon Balls again, we can
bring Kuririn-san, Chaozu-san,
and the others back to life, too!
Father, be sure you come back!
Let's call back Kuririn-san together,
using Planet Namek's Dragon Balls!
Kaio-sama, just what is going on?
What's happening to Goku and Freeza?
Freeza is dead.
As Freeza begged for his life,
Son Goku shared some of his Ki with him,
giving him a chance to live, but he...
Freeza used it to attack Goku.
And so, Goku had no choice
but to finish him off.
Then, Goku's victory is complete!
Mm-hmm, Freeza was no match for Goku,
once he became a Super Saiyan.
He did it!
That's how incredible a Super Saiyan is?
That means Goku's strength
is the greatest in the universe.
It seems like he's become
someone from a world far away.
However... However...
...he may only be the best in
the universe for a brief moment.
How so?
Planet Namek's explosion is closing in.
There isn't time for Goku to
reach the spaceship he came in.
He is headed for Freeza's
spaceship, which is nearby,
but it appears to be broken down, as well.
H-Hey, this is Goku. I'm sure
he'll scrape through somehow.
I mean, he's gotten out of
pinches like this time and again.
Besides, right now, Goku is
a Super Saiyan. Am I right?
Y-Yeah!
Goku, hurry! Just hurry!
All right!
Please, let me be in time!
Where's the control room?!
All right, good! It's almost the
same as the spaceship I came in!
Where's the takeoff button?!
Here!
Start up!
Please, start up!
Start up! Start up, damn it!
Start up! Start up!
Start up! Start up! Start up! Start up!
How can this be...? How can this--
What happened, Kaio-sama?!
His last remaining hope, Freeza's spaceship...
...has been swallowed up by lava...!
So then, what about Goku-san?
He can't make it back. All he can
do is share Planet Namek's fate.
It's going to explode.
Planet Namek is going to explode.
Damn it all!!
I can't watch!
Goku...
Goku... Don't you die...
Don't you die!!
Damn it all!!
Yeah! Break! Care! Break! As hard as you can
Fly away into the boundless skies
We'll hitch a ride on the jet stream,
and zip away to wherever we want
Being a daredevil is the best
Let's go tip-top! All right?
This eye-opening blue Earth of ours
is our irreplaceable world,
and we're not giving it up
Blast offa Kamehame-Ha
You were born
to protect the world in these uncertain times
Yeah! Break! Care! Break! As hard as you can
Go at it full power
Hope is my weapon,
so believe in the future
Yo, it's Yamucha!
Bulma, I want you to keep calm and listen to me.
Goku is... Goku is dead.
Hey, everyone! Word is that
Son-kun died. That's a shocker, huh?
Y-You dumbass! How can you put it like that?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z Kai,
"Goku Vanishes into Space...
Back to Life, Super Warriors!”
Huh? Son-kun can't be brought back to life?